[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "What is your take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "It's such a tragedy really the way that things have unfolded in Iraq.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "How significant is this, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, first of all, it needs to be substantiated if those chemical weapons were, in fact, used.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "And if turns out Assad has got them and has used them against the rebels, what is the proportionate reaction should come from America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, let's put this into context.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How do we know who to believe here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Well, you start by not believing the people who lied to you before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "You're talking about Obama versus Bush?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "What it is is -- first of all we set this thing up to where we supported the Shiites and the Sunnis are now -- there is going to be a version of a civil war.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "It's a bit late, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "But -- how -- if you get a war wrong what are the repercussions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "WRB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Well, I have so many things to say we don't have time to cover them all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "He won't come on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I have repeatedly asked him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "What can they do if their politicians are simply too cowardly to act on their behalf because of the power of the NRA?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "People are going to have to let these politicians know that they're going to be voted out in the next term.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "In other words, it was right home to them and their families?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, I think we all know the answer to that question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Michael, why the change of mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, your people, your producers have called me since Aurora.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Where are the people who -- as Robert Kennedy brilliantly said, where is this -- the moral leadership?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel Maddow"]}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Which show is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Rachel Maddow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "So you do DVR the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "What is wrong with people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "There is a ton of money being made right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "What's the answer, Michael?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "There is only one answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Reid"]}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "The next school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I wonder -- I would ask that to Harry Reid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "How about 1,050 children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "I want him to explain himself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Francis", "Virgin Mary"], "LOCATION": ["Assisi"]}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Well, growing up in our house, Francis of Assisi was like -- you know, he was right up there with the Virgin Mary because of what he stood for, his concern for the poor, environment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130319pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "What do you want to say about the new Pope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "He has -- well, let me -- I want to be optimistic right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]